<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Facebook	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 04:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Eric		</title>
		<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/#comment-4288</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 04:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/?p=1570#comment-4288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On Grand Mighty! lol]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Grand Mighty! lol</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Wang		</title>
		<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/#comment-4238</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 05:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/?p=1570#comment-4238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[how the hell am i supposed to talk to you about grandmighty now?]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>how the hell am i supposed to talk to you about grandmighty now?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Kent		</title>
		<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/#comment-3903</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 04:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/?p=1570#comment-3903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[haha, I feel you dude. It&#039;s like, I&#039;m &quot;friends&quot; with some folks. Big example is my &quot;ex&quot;. Sure, we are on good ol Facebook, but we don&#039;t even &quot;talk&quot; and what not. For goodness sake, I even blocked her from my News Feed, I might as well have deleted her. =P But I feel you man. It&#039;s probably best that I at least not spend my WHOLE day on the internet just for liking status messages and commenting on stuff. =P That&#039;s what photo portfolios like Flickr/and blogs and phones are for calling/texting are, right? lol But there ARE those people who do NOTHING more than stay on that ALL day. I do have to admit, I&#039;m probably pretty close to being one of those people. Maybe that&#039;s why I haven&#039;t blogged or even read your blog for awhile. =P]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>haha, I feel you dude. It&#8217;s like, I&#8217;m &#8220;friends&#8221; with some folks. Big example is my &#8220;ex&#8221;. Sure, we are on good ol Facebook, but we don&#8217;t even &#8220;talk&#8221; and what not. For goodness sake, I even blocked her from my News Feed, I might as well have deleted her. =P But I feel you man. It&#8217;s probably best that I at least not spend my WHOLE day on the internet just for liking status messages and commenting on stuff. =P That&#8217;s what photo portfolios like Flickr/and blogs and phones are for calling/texting are, right? lol But there ARE those people who do NOTHING more than stay on that ALL day. I do have to admit, I&#8217;m probably pretty close to being one of those people. Maybe that&#8217;s why I haven&#8217;t blogged or even read your blog for awhile. =P</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Eric		</title>
		<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/#comment-3901</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eric]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/?p=1570#comment-3901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Definitely, the level of value Facebook offers will vary from person to person. I mainly wrote this post to open up thought, because without controversy, things can get stale :-) 

The decision is purely yours and there is no right or wrong either way... I might reactivate my Facebook, because as you said, there are some people that you primarily contact now through there... but will be deleting all &quot;friends&quot; that I don&#039;t really know or keep in contact with anymore. We&#039;ll see how that goes, if it still sucks then I&#039;m done with it. I must say, it has been nice not having to check it though... ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Definitely, the level of value Facebook offers will vary from person to person. I mainly wrote this post to open up thought, because without controversy, things can get stale :-) </p>
<p>The decision is purely yours and there is no right or wrong either way&#8230; I might reactivate my Facebook, because as you said, there are some people that you primarily contact now through there&#8230; but will be deleting all &#8220;friends&#8221; that I don&#8217;t really know or keep in contact with anymore. We&#8217;ll see how that goes, if it still sucks then I&#8217;m done with it. I must say, it has been nice not having to check it though&#8230; </p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Kent		</title>
		<link>https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/2011/03/facebook/#comment-3899</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kent]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 04:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://grandmighty.github.io/grandmighty/?p=1570#comment-3899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In many ways, this is true. Like everything else, there are the ups-and-downs of everything, like this. I do admit, it is very time-consuming but it is quite a simple way of having to contacting folks through means of the internet. Like me, I have a jazz accordion band that keeps in contact with each other with events and what not. I guess because a lot of us are actually really &quot;active&quot; on there, therefore, depend on such a thing to keep on contact. But whatever though, it is nice to take a &quot;breather&quot; from Facebook because many people DO participate in this social network. But yea, what you said, I do agree on many levels and have to admit that I too am a victim of this. =P Oh well. lol (hope I even had a train of thought with this comment).]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In many ways, this is true. Like everything else, there are the ups-and-downs of everything, like this. I do admit, it is very time-consuming but it is quite a simple way of having to contacting folks through means of the internet. Like me, I have a jazz accordion band that keeps in contact with each other with events and what not. I guess because a lot of us are actually really &#8220;active&#8221; on there, therefore, depend on such a thing to keep on contact. But whatever though, it is nice to take a &#8220;breather&#8221; from Facebook because many people DO participate in this social network. But yea, what you said, I do agree on many levels and have to admit that I too am a victim of this. =P Oh well. lol (hope I even had a train of thought with this comment).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
